{
    "subject": "resource/Charles_Hibbert_Tupper",
    "predicate": "property/shortDescription",
    "object": "Canadian politician",
    "human_readable": "Charles Hibbert Tupper is a Canadian politician.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.925778329372406,
            "question": "Was Charles Hibbert Tupper involved in politics?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.792197048664093,
            "question": "What country is Charles Hibbert Tupper associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7893221378326416,
            "question": "Where was Charles Hibbert Tupper from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7728151679039001,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Charles Hibbert Tupper's political career?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7634936571121216,
            "question": "During what time period was Charles Hibbert Tupper active in politics?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7479217052459717,
            "question": "What profession did Charles Hibbert Tupper have?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7465639710426331,
            "question": "What political party was Charles Hibbert Tupper affiliated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6078771352767944,
            "question": "What were some of Charles Hibbert Tupper's accomplishments?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45926326513290405,
            "question": "Are there any notable events associated with Charles Hibbert Tupper's life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4316929876804352,
            "question": "Is there any information available about Charles Hibbert Tupper's personal life?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Charles Hibbert Tupper is a Canadian politician.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7290_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any notable events associated with Charles Hibbert Tupper's life?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7290_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What were some of Charles Hibbert Tupper's accomplishments?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7290_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What political party was Charles Hibbert Tupper affiliated with?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7290_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7290_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7290_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7290_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7290_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7290_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7290_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7290_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7290_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7290_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7290_7.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have any other queries!"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Sir Charles Hibbert Tupper, indicating that he was indeed a Canadian politician. The details include his roles such as Member of Parliament and various ministerial positions, confirming the statement that Charles Hibbert Tupper is a Canadian politician."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}